

Contact

ali.fattahian1378@gmail.com

ali-fattahian.com

Shahrekord, Iran

+98-913-482-2507

Skills

Python

Javascript

 HTML

CSS/SASS

Django

Django REST Framework

React

Redux

Test Driven Development

Git

Languages

English

Persian

Ali Fattahian

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

About me

Full stack web developer with 3 years of experience excited at the prospect of collaborating with colleagues and improving my skills as a developer in a professional setting. Detail-oriented worker with effective creative thinking and problemsolving skills. Looking to apply my understanding of Python, JavaScript and Web Technologies: Django, REST APIs and React at your company.

Experience

Prime Connect 5/2023 - 08/2023

- Technologies used: Python, Javascript, Postgres, HTML, CSS, Django, Django REST framework, React, Blurhash, and JWT authentication.
- E-commerce website with a focus on performance, accessibility, and user experience.
- Fully functional admin panel with analytics of sales based on countries, product categories, and time.

Twitter(X) clone 04/2022 - 06/2022

- Technologies used: Python, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Postgres,
 Django, Django REST framework, React and JWT authentication.
- Python threading for email validation for a better user experience.
- User profiles with features such as bio, profile picture, and background image with an asynchronous checking of existing usernames for editing and creating profiles.
- Following/follower and user suggestion system
- Search, bookmark, reply, and like features

Techie Tweed Blog 08/2021 - 11/2021

- Technologies used: Python, Django, HTML, CSS, Postgres, Django DBBackup, Ckeditor, Cloudinary, Django Whitenoise, and Session based Authentication system
- Automatic weekly database backup system

Education

(2019-2023) Bachelor's degree in software engineering

Islamic Azad University

ECTS: A